Your Royal Highness. Forgive me.
Lawrence?
He's always late.
Does it deliberately, I'm sure.
My lecture at the RGS overran horribly.
You're in great demand.
everyone wanting to have their photograph taken with you. It's most tiresome.
Ha Ha Ha
Ah, Philby, old man. Long time no see. I trust the Foreign Office is making full use of your talents.
Lawrence.
And you must be Prince Faisal.
Not finding England too chilly, I trust?
On the contrary, the weather is most climate.
Spoken like a true Englishman.
Mark my words, there is a revolt brewing in Mesopotamia. We must honor the promise of self-government as laid out in the Anglo-French declaration.
Wouldn't you agree, Philby?
I would.
Absolutely.
And we must let Faisal bin Hussein govern Mesopotamia. He is, in my estimation, the finest Arab leader since Saladin.
If I may.
No man commands more respect across Arabia than Prince Faisal's father, Abdulaziz Al Saud.
Abdulaziz Al Saud.
This I learned when I rode right into the heart of Hussein's territory.
You may wonder how I could enter the kingdom of the Hejaz unannounced, with no invitation, like the sun in the sky as old Hussein protested.
Because I traveled on the authority of Al Saud.
We have no greater friend in the whole of Arabia.
What do you see, Prince Faisal
Is it true? Could your father, the Emir, one day be King of all Arabia?
I thought an Englishman never discussed politics over the dinner table.
How's the restoration going?
Never buy a castle, Montague.
Gertrude Bell's most persuasive on the matter. You must read her report.
He's keep avoiding me
Wait until he's drunk his first whiskey.
Your master has asked for mint tea. Would you be kind enough to show us how it is made?
Of course.
Over there.
How is the dinner going?
All good.
You simply don't have the resources to maintain control of Mesopotamia.
Day after day, week after week, there is a continuance of this wasteful, miserable, sporadic warfare.
yeah.
Not a single friend in the press upon the subject.
Cradle of civilization and they can't afford the ink.
Doesn't this remind you of being at home?
The men discussing affairs of state.
I feel most at home.
Before you leave for Arabia, you must come to my club as my guest. The food there is excellent.
I would like that very much, Lord Curzon.
But
I hope we can have another meeting first.
In private.
by time you went back to the desert.
What the bloody hell! You did that on purpose.
No, it was an accident.
Marzuq, apologize. Do something.
I apologize most sincerely. He's still learning.
Splendid evening your highness.
yes.
but not as good food as at the lisay palace
please excuse me.
Where's Marzuq.
he's in the Stables.
Marzuq.
I have failed you.
No. We are brothers and between us not a drop of water must come.
Forgive me.
Remember. When we arrived in Plymouth
I saw the huge ship.
The might of the British Navy.
a British Navy
I felt so small.
So in awe.
Why should the British listen to me?
A boy from the desert?
Because you are Prince Faisal bin Abdulaziz.
am I really.
You are a prince amongst men.
tell me something. was it  an accident when you spled the tea over Montague.
No. I never liked that man.
we are going home.
We are lost.
No.
We are going back to our real home.
to Arabia.